<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on NijiGPen Documentation</title>
    <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on NijiGPen Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boolean</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/bool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/bool/</guid>
      <description>Boolean#NijiGPen provides following 2D boolean operations on the closed paths of two or more strokes:
Union (Sum, OR) Difference (Subtract, NOT) Intersection (AND) Exclusive (XOR) These functions are realized by calling the Clipper library. Please check the link for more details.
Edit Mode Operators#There are multiple buttons in the Edit mode panel, which are shortcuts of the same operator. This operator takes the paths of selected strokes as the input, and generate new strokes which are results of the boolean operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brush Import</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/brushes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/brushes/</guid>
      <description>Brush Import#The ABR/GBR Brushes button is an operator that converts .abr and .gbr brush files, which are widely used in software including Adobe Photoshop, GIMP and Krita, into Grease Pencil materials/brushes.
It may take a long time to parse high resolution (e.g. 2500px * 2500px) brushes, because the brush images need to be uncompressed. The time further increases if the file contains multiple brushes.
If you want to use the high resolution brushes repeatedly, you may consider save the brushes in a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frame Animations</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/animation/frame_animation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/animation/frame_animation/</guid>
      <description>Frame Animations#Multiframe Operations#Grease Pencil has a Multiframe Tool allowing users to draw or edit on multiple frames at the same time. Some of NijiGPen&amp;rsquo;s operators in the Edit mode support this feature. With the Multiframe tool enabled, they are performed on all selected frames, instead of the active frame.
In addition, new options will appear in the multiframe mode for some operators, which are designed for making animated effects, including:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Packages</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/get_started/installation/dependency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/get_started/installation/dependency/</guid>
      <description>Python Packages#NijiGPen&amp;rsquo;s functionality relies on some third-party Python packages, which have to be separately downloaded and installed. If you have no experience with Blender add-ons that have similar requirements, it is strongly suggested to read this page before using the add-on.
Dependency Summary#The table below lists the packages required for each type of operation. Lacking a package will not affect operations that do not require it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scene Setup</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/tips/scene_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/tips/scene_setup/</guid>
      <description>Scene Setup#Blender comes with a template start file &amp;ldquo;2D Animation&amp;rdquo; that is convenient for painting. However, there are also some tricky parts in setting up the scene, especially when we put Grease Pencil and 3D objects in the same scene, including the meshes generated by this add-on. Here are some tips written in the form of FAQ.
Why cannot I see any shading effect when I generate meshes from Grease Pencil?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Usage</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/get_started/basic_usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/get_started/basic_usage/</guid>
      <description>Basic Usage#User Interface#NijiGPen creates new user interfaces to trigger its functions in the following places of Blender.
Sidebar Panels#A tab named NijiGP will appear in the sidebar of the 3D Viewport, if the active object is Grease Pencil and the mode is Draw, Edit or Weight Paint. This is the major way of calling NijiGPen&amp;rsquo;s functions.
NijiGPen operators are categorized in several panels. Depending on the current mode, different panels or operators may appear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limitations</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/tips/limitations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/tips/limitations/</guid>
      <description>Limitations#The add-on has a number of limitations in different aspects, including:
Unfinished features of the add-on itself, which may be improved in future releases. Limitations due to Blender&amp;rsquo;s own design, which may lead to different behaviors from common graphics software. This page lists limitations which are general to multiple operators. Besides it, the constraints of 2D space can be found in Basic Usage. The limitation of each single operator will be recorded in their own page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rigging Utilities</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/animation/rigging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/animation/rigging/</guid>
      <description>Rigging Utilities#Although Blender can automatically generate weights rigging Grease Pencil strokes to an armature, the result often requires heavy manual adjustment. NijiGPen provides with several alternative methods generating bone weights.
The rigging-related operations will show up in a panel when the current mode is Weight Paint.
Transfer Weights from Meshes#The Weight From Meshes button is a tool transferring the weights from rigged mesh objects to the current Grease Pencil object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSD Render</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/psd_render/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/psd_render/</guid>
      <description>PSD Render#The Multi-Layer PSD Render button renders each layer of the Grease Pencil object to a separate image, and then merge them together to a .psd file. The name, blend mode of each layer and the sequence of layers will be preserved. In this way, the image can be further edited in various popular image editing or painting software.
Besides the Grease Pencil layers, there are two additional PSD layers rendered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Fill</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/line/smart_fill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/line/smart_fill/</guid>
      <description>Smart Fill#Smart Fill is an operator in the Draw mode. It fills an entire line art layer based on some color hints marked by the user. Compared with the Blender&amp;rsquo;s default Fill tool, it has the following advantages:
It handles the gaps in the line art automatically. It is less likely to leave seams near the contour, or be intersected. Although the algorithms are different, the concept of this operation is similar to the Colorize Mask tool in Krita.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vectorizing Images</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/vectorizing_images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/vectorizing_images/</guid>
      <description>Vectorizing Images#The Trace Image to Grease Pencil tool of Blender is limited to black and white input images. NijiGPen provides with operators vectorizing another two types of raster images.
These operators take either a single image or an image sequence as the input, and generate new strokes in the current Grease Pencil layer. The direction of the generated strokes is parallel to the current 2D working plane.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
