<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>- Import/Export - on NijiGPen Documentation</title>
    <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in - Import/Export - on NijiGPen Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brush Import</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/brushes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/brushes/</guid>
      <description>Brush Import#Through the Import/Export sidebar panel, the user can load brushes of some other painting software&#39;s file formats into Blender and extract their textures to create Grease Pencil materials/brushes. Currently, the following formats are supported:
.abr brushes that are commonly used in Adobe Photoshop, GIMP and Krita. .gbr brushes of GIMP. .brush or .brushset files exported from Procreate. .sut brushes exported from Clip Studio Paint. Please be sure to follow the license and terms of service of the original brush, especially for those acquired from an asset store, which usually prohibits some behaviors such as redistribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palette Import</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/colors/</guid>
      <description>Palette Import#Through the Import/Export sidebar panel, the user can import some palette/swatch files which contain color information. The add-on will convert them to Blender palettes. Currently, the following file formats are supported:
.aco files used by Adobe Photoshop and Clip Studio Paint. .swatches files used by Procreate. In addition, color codes can also be directly pasted to Blender. Please refer to the clipboard utilities for more information.Recolor with a Palette#The add-on also provides with a utility to quickly color the drawing using the imported palette.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clipboard Utilities</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/clipboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/clipboard/</guid>
      <description>Clipboard Utilities#NijiGPen provides with the clipboard enhancement that allows users to paste specific types of data produced by other graphic editing software.
Paste SVG Codes#It is common for graphic design software to copy vector shapes as SVG code, including a small amount of painting software such as Clip Studio Paint. You can directly paste the shapes inside the current Grease Pencil object through NijiGPen.
The parsing of SVG codes is in the same way as the standard import function of Blender, except for an additional option to automatically detect holes in imported shapes and make them transparent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vectorizing Images</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/vectorizing_images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/vectorizing_images/</guid>
      <description>Vectorizing Images#The Trace Image to Grease Pencil tool of Blender is limited to black and white input images. NijiGPen provides with operators vectorizing another two types of raster images.
These operators take either a single image or an image sequence as the input, and generate new strokes in the current Grease Pencil layer. The direction of the generated strokes is parallel to the current 2D working plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSD Render</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/psd_render/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/io/psd_render/</guid>
      <description>PSD Render#The Multi-Layer PSD Render button renders each layer of the Grease Pencil object to a separate image, and then merge them together to a .psd file. The name, blend mode of each layer and the sequence of layers will be preserved. In this way, the image can be further edited in various popular image editing or painting software.
Besides the Grease Pencil layers, there are two additional PSD layers rendered.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
