<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>- Polygons - on NijiGPen Documentation</title>
    <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in - Polygons - on NijiGPen Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boolean</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/bool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/bool/</guid>
      <description>Boolean#NijiGPen provides following 2D boolean operations on the closed paths of two or more strokes:
Union (Sum, OR) Difference (Subtract, NOT) Intersection (AND) Exclusive (XOR) These functions are realized by calling the Clipper library. Please check the link for more details.
Edit Mode Operators#There are multiple buttons in the Edit mode panel, which are shortcuts of the same operator. This operator takes the paths of selected strokes as the input, and generate new strokes which are results of the boolean operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offset</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/offset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/offset/</guid>
      <description>Offset#The 2D Offset operation is performed on the path of a stroke to achieve inflating/deflating/beveling of the shape.
Although Blender has some inset/bevel operators/modifiers, they are not available for Grease Pencil. Besides, compared with Blender&#39;s method, this add-on will not cause the self-intersection of the output shape.
These functions are realized by calling the Clipper library. Please check the link for more details.
From Sidebar Panel#The Offset button in the sidebar panel will offset each selected stroke with a given length value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweep</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/sweep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/sweep/</guid>
      <description>Sweep#The Sweep operation drags stroke polygons along a given vector or path to create several effects, such as the pseudo-3D extrusion and shadowing.
The mathematical terminology behind this concept is Minkowski sum.
From Sidebar Panel#The Sweep button in the sidebar panel performs the operation on each selected stroke by typing the lengths of a 2D vector.
Shape Style#The following 3 styles apply:
Extrude: It turns the shapes into a pseudo-3D look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hole Holdout</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/holdout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/holdout/</guid>
      <description>Hole Holdout#To display holes inside a shape&#39;s fill, Blender has a unique mechanism in Grease Pencil that is different from most vector graphic editing software. Users need to manually enable a Holdout option in the material setting to make a stroke transparent.
To simplify this process, NijiGPen provides with an operator to automatically detect holes among selected strokes. If a stroke&#39;s path is completely inside another stroke&#39;s fill:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatch Fill</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/hatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/functionality/polygon/hatch/</guid>
      <description>Hatch Fill#This is an Edit mode operator to generate doodle or hatch patterns inside the selected stroke shapes. Various types of stylized shading or coloring effects can be achieved with different combinations of options.
Line Styles#The operator will generate a grid of points inside each selected shape, while there are multiple ways to connect these points as new strokes:
Single-Line Doodle: In this mode, all points will be connected together to ensure that each input stroke generates only one output stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
