<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Developer Notes on NijiGPen Documentation</title>
    <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/developer_notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Developer Notes on NijiGPen Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/developer_notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm Design</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/developer_notes/algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/developer_notes/algorithms/</guid>
      <description>Algorithm Design#This page provides an in-depth exploration of the algorithms utilized by this add-on, both for developers interested in vector graphics processing and for users wondering about the core principles underlying the add-on’s functionality.
It is less recommended to read the source code directly, since the code details are not excellent and still need refinement. Instead, this article focuses more on the mathematics behind each feature.
The add-on’s functions fall into two categories:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Structures</title>
      <link>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/developer_notes/data_structures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chsh2.github.io/nijigp/docs/developer_notes/data_structures/</guid>
      <description>Data Structures#Despite the new operators, this add-on prefers an unobtrusive style that does not change the original way that Blender&#39;s objects work. However, a small number of operators must create new properties/attributes in an object to store additional information. This pages list all new data structures created by the add-on.
Add-On Registering#All add-on operators are registered under bpy.ops.gpencil with the name prefix nijigp_. The add-on chooses gpencil as the category instead of creating a new one, because this allows users to assign shortcut to each operator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
